let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "WHO INVENTED PYTHON?",
        answer: "C.  Guido van Rossum ",
        options: [
            "A. ADA",
            "B. SULTON",
            "C.  Guido van Rossum ",
            "D. Charles Barbage"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "WHO IS THE FATHER OF COMPUTER?",
        answer: "D. CHARLES BARBAGE",
        options: [
            "A. CHARLES DARWIN",
            "B. THOMAS BARBAGE",
            "C. SALZ SAVAGE",
            "D. CHARLES BARBAGE"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "WHO INVENTED C?",
        answer: "C. Dennis Ritchie",
        options: [
            "A. Ada Lovelace",
            "B. Karl Mars",
            "C. Dennis Ritchie",
            "D. Elon Musk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "WHICH LANGUAGE CAN BE USED FOR BOTH FRONTEND AND BACKEND?",
        answer: "C. JAVASCRIPT",
        options: [
            "A. C", 
            "B. JAVA",
            "C. JAVASCRIPT",
            "D. RUBY"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "WHICH IS NOT A PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE",
        answer: "B. C+",
        options: [
            "A. C",
            "B. C+",
            "C. C++",
            "D. C#"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "WHICH LANGUAGE IS USED FOR DATABASE MANAGEMENT?",
        answer: "B. SQL",
        options: [
            "A. JAVASCRIPT",
            "B. SQL",
            "C. RUBY",
            "D. PHP"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "WHICH IS THE FASTEST PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE?",
        answer: "A. C++",
        options: [
            "A. C++",
            "B. JAVA",
            "C. JAVASCRIPT",
            "D. PASCAL"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "WHATS THE FIRST COMPUTER PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE?",
        answer: "D. ADA",
        options: [
            "A. JAVA",
            "B. C",
            "C. FOTRAIN",
            "D. ADA"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "WHO INVENTED PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE?",
        answer: "D. ADA LOVELACE",
        options: [
            "A. CHARLES BARBAGE", 
            "B. BENEDICT CUCUMBATCH",
            "C. DENNIE RITCHIE",
            "D. ADA LOVELACE"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "WHICH PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE IS USED FOR GAME DEVELOPMENT?",
        answer: "D. ALL OF THE ABOVE",
        options: [
            "A. C++",
            "B. JAVA",
            "C. PYTHON",
            "D. ALL OF THE ABOVE"
        ]
    },
];